(Sheldon:)if we shore up
our weak link,
(Sheldon:)which is clearly
Leonard as Superman.
(Leonard:)Hey, I got
new boots this year.
(Leonard:)Guaranteed to add
three inches.
(Sheldon:)That's sad.
Let's ask ourselves:
(Sheldon:)Is there anyone we know
(Sheldon:)who would make a more manly
and convincing son of Krypton?
(Stuart:)Than Leonard
in high-heeled boots?
(Stuart:)Howard's mother
(Sheldon:)I was thinking specifically
of the gentleman over there
(Sheldon:)moving his lips
as he enjoys
(Sheldon:)the latest exploits
of Betty and Veronica.
(Leonard:)Zack?
(Howard:)He is the only person we know
with actual muscles.
(Leonard:)You can't replace
me with Zack.
(Sheldon:)Why not?
Penny did it.
(Howard:)Yeah, she seems happier.
(Howard:)Why wouldn't we be?